{
  "level": 2,
  "unit": 3,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "To go _____________ something is to go from one side to the other.",
          "answer": "across"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you _____________ something, you take it and agree to return it later.",
          "answer": "borrow"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ is land that is away from cities or large towns.",
          "answer": "countryside"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An _____________ is a thought or plan you have for something.",
          "answer": "ideas"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If my mom _____________ on something, she says firmly that it must be done.",
          "answer": "insists"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ place is one that very few people visit.",
          "answer": "lonely"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a way to answer a problem.",
          "answer": "solution"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are very small towns in the country.",
          "answer": "villages"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "If someone likes _____________, they like doing exciting and unusual things.",
          "answer": "adventure"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you feel _____________, you feel very pleased about something.",
          "answer": "delighted"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you _____________ about something you would like to have happen, you imagined it happening.",
          "answer": "dreamed"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you _____________ doing something, you like doing it.",
          "answer": "enjoyed"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If your friends _____________, they complained about something.",
          "answer": "grumbled"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the Moonâ€™s glow, which you often see at night.",
          "answer": "moonlight"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a person who lives near you.",
          "answer": "neighbor"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the dark part of the day.",
          "answer": "nighttime"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means shouted with happiness or praise.",
          "answer": "cheered"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a performance by musicians or singers.",
          "answer": "concert"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An _____________ is a tool used to do or make something.",
          "answer": "instrument"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Our _____________ are our ways of moving.",
          "answer": "movements"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the pleasing sounds made by a singer or musical instrument, such as a piano or guitar.",
          "answer": "music"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the repeating accents of sounds or movements to create a beat.",
          "answer": "rhythm"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are noises that can be heard.",
          "answer": "sounds"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you _____________ something you know what it means.",
          "answer": "understand"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
